





Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Summary

2 years 8 months of functional experience include technical and analytical working experience in advance Excel.

Worked with cross functional team, interacting with management an efficiently getting the work done in timely manner.

Strong analytical and problem solving skill as well as excellence oral and written communication

Work Experience

- Concentrix Technologies India Pvt. Ltd as Technical Support Engineer, Advisor II Dec 2020 to Till Date
- Wipro Limited as Trust and Safety Quality Analyst May 2019 to Nov 2020

Key responsibilities area to take care the quality for the team along with floor. Need to take a session, to discuss about the process doc. and process improvement plan. Client calibration,RCA and Feedback are the most important part for daily work.

Wipro Limited as L1 Technical Support Engineer Feb 2018 to May 2019

1 years 2 months of functional experience include technical and analytical working experience in advance Excel, application support, provide solutions to windows related problem, and incident management.

Worked with cross functional team, interacting with management an efficiently getting the work done in timely manner.

Strong analytical and problem solving skill as well as excellence oral and written communication

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Jis College of Engineering in 2017

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Bluemix Essentials

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Root Cause Analysis		0	1 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
EXCEL			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
MS OUTLOOK			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
MS OFFICE			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
TEAM MANAGEMENT			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
DATA ANALYSIS			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
HTML			
CSS			
Content Analysis			2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
SQL			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient			✓
Bengali	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Google - YT

Client: Google

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: Bangalore

Role: Quality Analyst

Duration: Feb 2018 - Oct 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 26

Skill Used: Root cause analysis, Ms office, Ms outlook, Ms Excel, Google sheets work, Team management, analytical skills, Data analysis.

Role Description: Key responsibilities area to take care the quality for the team along with floor. Need to take a session, to discuss about the process doc. and process improvement plan. Client calibration,RCA and Feedback are the most important part for daily work.

Project Details: The project all about contact analysis, contents are basically depends on real life even. Based on SOP and urgent guidelines we are supposed to take action.

As an Quality Analyst, I have to Audit for others admin of Wipro along with different vendors.

Need to attend Client Calibration call to deep discussion about the contents.

Team session, RCA, and Feedback also most important part of our daily work.

Need to work on ad-hoc task and SLA as per Client requirements.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.